<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>python on Jordan Uyeki</title>
    <link>https://jordanuyeki.github.io/techs/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in python on Jordan Uyeki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Jordan Uyeki</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jordanuyeki.github.io/techs/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Face Mask Detection</title>
      <link>https://jordanuyeki.github.io/portfolio/mask_detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordanuyeki.github.io/portfolio/mask_detection/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Project Overview The Data Neural Network Models Results Future Directions
Project Overview  Over a year in and the COVID-19 pandemic is still as present as ever - and with that, wearing masks in public places has become the new normal. Despite much resistance, mask wearing is critical to keep the general population safe and minimize the spread of the virus.
The goal of this project was to build a neural network model which could be used to determine whether or not people are wearing face masks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animal Shelter Outcome Predictions</title>
      <link>https://jordanuyeki.github.io/portfolio/shelter_predictions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jordanuyeki.github.io/portfolio/shelter_predictions/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Project Overview The Data Data Preparation and Feature Engineering Modeling Results Future Directions
For a video walkthrough of my project, please see this youtube video.
Project Overview  According to the ASPCA, pet adoption rates skyrocketed across the United States during the COVID-19 pandemic, with nearly 1 in 5 American households adopting a new furry friend into their family. My family was among those who adopted a new pet during the pandemic - in August 2020, we adopted my bestie, Bolt!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
